[
  {
      "title" : "Premier League"
  },


  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Name the all-time top 10 goal scorers in the Premier League",
    "answer": "Alan Shearer"
  },
  {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Name the all-time top 10 goal scorers in the Premier League",
      "answer": "Harry Kane"
  },

  {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Name the all-time top 10 goal scorers in the Premier League",
      "answer": "Wayne Rooney"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Name the all-time top 10 goal scorers in the Premier League",
        "answer": "Andy Cole"
    },

  {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Name the all-time top 10 goal scorers in the Premier League",
      "answer": "Sergio Aguero"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Name the all-time top 10 goal scorers in the Premier League",
        "answer": "Frank Lampard"
    },

  {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Name the all-time top 10 goal scorers in the Premier League",
      "answer": "Thiery Henry"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Name the all-time top 10 goal scorers in the Premier League",
        "answer": "Mohammed Salah"
    },

  {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Name the all-time top 10 goal scorers in the Premier League",
      "answer": "Robbie Fowler"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Name the all-time top 10 goal scorers in the Premier League",
        "answer": "Jermaine Defoe"
    }
]
